[
  {
    "id": 41,
    "question": "For all he cared, the game was as good as lost.",
    "options": [
      "He did not care if the game was lost",
      "He could not care less if the game was lost",
      "He was almost certain that the game would be lost",
      "He was afraid the game would be lost",
      "The game was very good, and he cared very much about losing it"
    ],
    "ans": "A",
    "main": "",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "question": "A basic object in this respect is the attainment of self sufficiency in food in about a decade.",
    "options": [
      "Food will soon be sufficient for every body",
      "Mass production of food",
      "We should aim at producing food for sale and consumption in ten years",
      "We should be able to feed ourselves in five years",
      "Our aim is to provide enough food for our needs"
    ],
    "ans": "E",
    "main": "attainment of self sufficiency in food in about a decade",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "question": "The manager said that unless the employees worked harder the factory would have to be closed. That manager said that ___",
    "options": [
      "the employees were not working hard, and so the factory would be closed",
      "the employees should not close early so that they could produce more",
      "the factory was not productive because the employees were lazy",
      "the factory would be shut if the employees did not increase their output",
      "the factory was closed because the employees did not work hard enough"
    ],
    "ans": "E",
    "main": "unless the employees worked harder the factory would have to be closed",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "question": "The new employee is so humble and friendly that he will soon make himself popular.",
    "options": [
      "welcomed and accepted",
      "hated",
      "estranged",
      "rejected",
      "a personal friend"
    ],
    "ans": "A",
    "main": "popular",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "question": "He lost his voice momentarily.",
    "options": [
      "in a moment",
      "in a split second",
      "for a brief period of time",
      "without delay",
      "instantly"
    ],
    "ans": "C",
    "main": "momentarily",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "question": "I am yet to write the penultimate paragraph of my essay.",
    "options": ["last but one", "third to the last", "second", "concluding"],
    "ans": "A",
    "main": "penultimate",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "question": "The Senate postponed the meeting indefinitely.",
    "options": [
      "for a short time",
      "for six months",
      "definitely",
      "without fixing a date",
      "for several months"
    ],
    "ans": "D",
    "main": "indefinitely",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "question": "Since his father's death, Osita has not been able to cope with the tasks of a family head.",
    "options": [
      "perform adequately",
      "tolerate",
      "accept",
      "assess properly",
      "manage"
    ],
    "ans": "E",
    "main": " to cope with",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "question": "It is sheer foolhardiness for unarmed policemen to pursue armed robbers.",
    "options": [
      "nonsense",
      "bravery",
      "foolishness",
      "stupidity",
      "foolish risk taking"
    ],
    "ans": "E",
    "main": "foolhardiness ",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "question": "The judge came down heavily on the accused person in his judgement.",
    "options": [
      "crashed heavily",
      "fell down headlong",
      "descended upon heavily",
      "imposed a stiff penalty",
      "crash landed on"
    ],
    "ans": "D",
    "main": "came down heavily",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "question": "You are free to leave the hall.",
    "options": ["at an advantage", "opportune", "at liberty", "right"],
    "ans": "C",
    "main": "free",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "question": "The culprits will surrender their loot to the Customs officials.",
    "options": ["give away", "give out", "give in", "give up"],
    "ans": "D",
    "main": "surrender",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "question": "\"Watch it! You could be followed\", said the robber.",
    "options": ["Look around", "Be sober", "Be vigilant", "Lookout"],
    "ans": "C",
    "main": "Watch it!",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "question": "Many candidates apply to read Law because it is a lucrative profession.",
    "options": [
      "brings plenty of profit",
      "brings high prestige",
      "brings quick money",
      "brings plenty of knowledge"
    ],
    "ans": "A",
    "main": "lucrative",
    "remark": ""
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "question": "The pressman said that his interview with the president was off the record.",
    "options": [
      "not written on government record books",
      "not intended for publication",
      "not taped",
      "written elsewhere other than in government records"
    ],
    "ans": "B",
    "main": "off the recod",
    "remark": ""
  }
]
